Hi everyone and welcome to a new video here on my channel. I always say the same thing.
Anyway, I'm going to show you some looks today I created with pieces from the Australian brand
Black Milk. A lot of fake leather, also some PVC and really cool leggings. So I hope you're going
to enjoy this video. Before I'm going to change, I want to show you my new Paradise pants though
because they are the newest model called Mixed Pants because they're a combination of the normal aesthetic pants and the ultra aesthetic pants.
So basically PVC look and four-letter look mixed together.
The good thing is you can wear any kind of shoes, shiny shoes, not shiny shoes.
and of course you have the normal paradise cut here in the legs but no zipper so this is a
zipperless pants with a nice design feature and I also have a discount code for paradise
for the leggings but also for lingerie so I'll wear everything and I'll write it down below
okay now on to the black note stuff and I'm going to start with this PVC skirt
This skirt is awesome and I love how tight it is here in the waistband because I often
have the problem that waistbands on skirts are too wide but this one is perfect.
It has a zipper in the back and it has a nice length and sits really snug here in the waist.
And I paired it with a see-through bodysuit from Marimua and a choker but I feel like
there's something missing.
a bit plain here so I'll add another belt now it's kind of round look from head to toe with
the silver accessory parts and I do not need the belt here to keep the skirt tight which is awesome
but it just adds another cool layer look whatever and it's a perfect basic I think they have it all
the title something like this is a collection piece so not always available
anyway I'm super glad I found this skirt
and I love the complete look I think it's a nice festival look for example
when I created this look I realized I kind of need a PVC bodysuit because I do
not have one but I think the mesh one does the job too. I love how skirt flies.
Okay I think it's super cute this outfit but I'll continue with the next one namely this
four letter bodysuit. I combined this bodysuit with the pants first and I'll do a skirt later
but I think it's a really cool look with the long arms and the thumb holes it's
really tight and snug and shiny also I love this design feature with these
v-shaped stitching here so it's not just a plain bodysuit but it has a bit of
personality and I went all in with this look because I added some pants and not
as any pants but faux leather pants so it's a whole faux leather look they have
a lot of decorative seams the whole leg up and down also on the backside also
added some matte heels to complete the look and the choker and I thought this
looks somehow super spacey I'm going to add just for fun of it some glasses so
what do you think do not look like some kind of superhero or super cop like the
fashion police just so cool accessories but I love them and I also like this look again I wasn't sure in the
beginning if I like the pants combined with the bodysuit but I think it's
really cool and I have a four leather skirt next which is kind of basically
the same design because it's the same brand Mani d'Avoire but as a skirt and I'll
see what of them I'm going to like better. I think I prefer this version
with the skirt as I said similar design to the pants but as a skirt with these
cool accessories here integrated into the skirt and also for the back looks
really nice I think this is a more wearable look compared to the pants look
so I can definitely see me going out like this or having a drink in our
favorite bar like this to be honest it's kind of metal alternative bar so I have
no problems going there dressed this way and there are two things I really hate
about the bodysuit though. 3, 2, I don't know. There's no zipper and it's really tight here
in the neck so every time I want to get into the bodysuit I have to have no kind of hairstyle
and better no makeup because it is pain in the ass to get into this with the full face
of makeup and hairstyle and also the arms are so short they look really long because I
am wearing the arms with the thumb holes but they are digging into my skin here
because they're too short and of course the fabric itself is stretchy
but still a lot of tension going on here and it really hurts basically so it's already really
red here one and all the bodysuit is also too short so it's not really comfortable
this is the full body view with the skirt i yeah i'm wearing it like this now now there are two
holes on the inside also not the greatest whatever and still i love this uh combination
So if the bodysuit would fit really good then this would be an awesome look together with the skirt
But yeah, I have one last black milk item
I want to show you and I know that it's going to be really comfortable because I already tried it
some
Leggings, but the fun thing is that they're burned out velvet Devoray coat
Fabric so bit see-through bit velvety and I'm going to show you
Last outfit with the leggings.
And I paired it with a leather jacket and put the belt on top of the leather jacket with a bra.
Normally, to be honest, I would just wear a bad t-shirt over this kind of leggings or some kind of t-shirt.
But I wanted to create a more sophisticated look for the video.
That's why I also paired the silver heels.
Because they're fun and they're an eye-catcher and they work pretty well together with the accessories, of course.
So the leggings are slightly see-through as I said. You can basically see my underwear. Not safe for work so to say but I love the look and it's so comfortable.
like this really stretchy velvety fabric that is kind of mixed between mesh and velvet I don't know
like I said it's called Devoré and I just love feeling and the comfort of it and I'm sure I'm
going to wear it at the upcoming festivals in the next week or the events I'm going to
just to chill so to say in a stylish way
all right oh by the way did I ask you about the pants or skirt situation from
the outfit before which version do you prefer and I totally destroyed the
zipper of the skirt when I tried to get out of it yeah well and I had to fit
because I had to get out of the bodysuit over my head and anyway yeah things you
don't really see because it's a struggle to change all the outfits all the time
not going to complain here I hope you had fun and I hope you liked the outfits
I created definitely found some cool stuff I'm going to wear again and yeah
don't forget to subscribe to my channel check out my patreon and see you in the
video. Bye!